Tolgonai - Junior Node.js (Nest.js)Backend developer

Кыргызстан , Бишкек | 720001 | +996773103437 | @aldmtvatg tolgonai022002@gmail.com | Linkedin | GitHub

\mathbf{C}_{1}	ıın	ım	arv	7
9	un	TITI	uı	y

I have experience in developing social and commercial projects on Node.JS and Nest.JS Framework as a backend developer in a team consisting of 6 people, where 2 team members are backend developers. I used PostgreSQL as a database, use Swagger for API documentation, Cloudinary for uploading files, deployed projects to the Heroku cloud service. Participated in <u>Hackathons</u>.

Experience

Practiced at Neobis - programmers Club (present - aug 2022)

Neo Cafe 05/2023 - 08/2023

The project implements a system that allows customers to place orders directly through a mobile application. Orders are easily transferred to the barista, which eliminates the need for service personnel to participate in order processing. The service staff is primarily responsible for the delivery of ready meals and payment processing, which increases the convenience of customer service, reduces waiting times and increases satisfaction.

- · For this project, I first built a database schema, coordinated it with the team, and used a Postgresql database to store and process data.
- A system of accounting for authorization and registration using JWT(JSON Web Tokens) has been developed, as well as the separation of rights into two user roles: administrator, user.
- The functionality for creating and editing menus has been developed:
- · Managing Ingredients: Ability to create and edit ingredients
- · Managing dishes: Create, edit and manage dishes, including adding ingredients to each dish
- Functionality has been developed for the user profile, editing and viewing their order history.

Girls For Girls 01/2023 - 04/2023

An educational platform that aims to support and inspire girls for their personal and professional development. The platform provides access to a variety of educational resources, mentoring and community, contributing to the confidence and success of girls in the future.

- Created an ER diagram of the database, used a PostgresSQL database to store the data.
- Developed functionality for creating, editing educational trainings and forums, as well as functionality for sorting trainings and forums by date of completion, by subject
- · Developed functionality for viewing and managing feedback, connected Google SMTP, for mailing to the mail
- · Development of functionality for creating and adding lecturers to trainings and forums

<u>Car Sharing 11/2022 - 12/2022</u>

The project is a web-based car rental platform. Users can easily select and book cars for a given period. The system automatically calculates the rental price, taking into account various tariffs and discounts, and provides convenient management of bookings and cars.

- · Developed a user authorization and authentication system using JWT technology (JSON Web Tokens) to ensure secure access to the platform.
- Developed a mechanism for calculating the cost of car rental based on selected tariffs, discounts and rental terms. Implemented automatic calculation on the server side.
- Developed functionality for booking cars by the user, taking into account restrictions such as the minimum rental duration and pauses between bookings.

Education and Certifications

Kyrgyz National University named after Jusup Balasagyn Kyrgyzstan , Bishkek Faculty of Technical Physics 09/2019 - 06/2023

Technical skills

Node.js, Nest.js, PostgreSQL, TypeORM, Swagger, Rest API, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, Git, Github, Postman, Trello, ER-diagramm

Languages: Russian, English, Kyrgyz